<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<EVENTLIST>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>0</ID>
		<BACKGROUND>FuckingNoobs.jpg</BACKGROUND>	
		<TITLE>Bug Spot</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>bugspot.jpg</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>
			&lt;br&gt;
			Bug spot, the on-spot debugging contest is not only about programming talent but also about applying the sheer knowledge to rectify errors. The challenge tests a programmer's ability to understand and respond to dissimilar codes. The art of rectification / debugging is difficult than conventional programming because it's not about what you know, it's about how much you know and how you apply those cognitive ideas to recognize errors and act upon them. The event tests the programmer in areas of speed, intellect and understanding.

		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>
&lt;br&gt;
1.  &#160; Programming languages used will be C and Java.&lt;br&gt;
2.  &#160; A group can have maximum of 3 members.&lt;br&gt;
Rounds&lt;br&gt;
1st ROUND- Will consist of 50 MCQs related to basic programming knowledge, duration of which will be 1 hour. &lt;br&gt;
2nd ROUND- Will consist of Maximum 10 Subjective debugging questions, where participants have to spot the Bug and suggest a solution.&lt;br&gt;
In case of any discrepancy, decision of event organizers will be final.</RULES>
		<TIMELINE> 
			&lt;br&gt;
1.  &#160; 1st Round will be held on 12th November, 2016.&lt;br&gt;
2. &#160;  2nd Round is scheduled on 13 November, 2016.&lt;br&gt;
3. &#160;  Event timings will be informed prior to Infotsav.&lt;br&gt;
		</TIMELINE>


		<!-- <DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/pinnacle.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Pinnacle Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS> -->
		<CONTACTS>
			&lt;h4&gt;Manish Das&lt;/h4&gt;
		    &lt;p&gt;
		        &lt;span class="phone"&gt;Phone:&lt;/span&gt;+91-9516656746
		        &lt;/br&gt;
		        &lt;span class="phone"&gt;E-mail: manishranger@gmail.com&lt;/span&gt;
		    &lt;/p&gt;
		    &lt;/br&gt;

			&lt;h4&gt;Vineet Gugloth&lt;/h4&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;
				&lt;span class="phone"&gt;Phone:&lt;/span&gt;+91-9491912800
				&lt;/br&gt;
				&lt;span class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;
			&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/br&gt;
			
			&lt;h4&gt;Ravi Chandra&lt;/h4&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;
				&lt;span class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9425780379
				&lt;/br&gt;
				&lt;span class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;rrravichandra3@gmail.com
			&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/br&gt;
		</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>

	<EVENT>	
		<ID>1</ID>
		<BACKGROUND>JPTGTIB1I6.jpg</BACKGROUND>
		<TITLE>Code Rush</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>coderush.jpg</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt;Do you feel compelled to demystify the truth? Do you have a knack for solving problems? The online programming contest is here for you . Show off your programming skills and let your rusty gears jingle in the disco of grey cells. After all, life doesn&apos;t give a second chance. So face your opponent in the battlefield and prove yourself a great warrior.
&lt;br&gt;

This year also a set of demanding problems awaits one and the standard has only got tougher and tougher. In this grueling test the more one solves, the higher he or she scores.
&lt;br&gt;

The code-crazy enthusiasts are invited to be a part of this mega event at CODECHEF (A Directi Educational Initiative). So, all the participants are requested to get registered on http://www.codechef.com prior to the commencement of the contest. Permitted languages to provide solution are C, C++ and Java. The details of the contest are as follows.
&lt;br&gt;

This mega event will be hosted at CODECHEF (A Directi Educational Initiative).
&lt;br&gt;
So, all the participants are requested to register on the hosting website www.codechef.com prior to the commencement of the contest. All the participants also have to be registered on www.infotsav.org with the same codechef handle to be eligible for the prizes.
&lt;br&gt;
Permitted languages to provide solution are C, C++ and Java.
&lt;br&gt;
Only students who are studying in graduate and post-graduate level in any Indian university are eligible for the prizes. Professionals can participate but are not eligible for the prizes.
&lt;br&gt;
Please do not discuss strategy, suggestions or tips in the comments during a live contest. If you are unsure, email us at coderush@infotsav.org.
&lt;br&gt;
You will receive one point for solving a problem (passing all test cases - no partial credit), regardless of the level of difficulty of that problem.
&lt;br&gt;
You can submit solutions as many times as you'd like, there are no penalties for incorrect submissions. Users are ranked according to the most problems solved. Ties will be broken by the total time for each user in ascending order of time.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;Any participant found having fake information regarding qualification criteria or profile information shall be immediately disqualified.
&lt;br&gt;
After the end of the contest, the test cases and the author's solution would be available on the page www.facebook.com/Coderush.Infotsav.
&lt;br&gt;
Any sort of malicious activity will lead to immediate disqualification of the participant in question.
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt; The decision of the organizers in declaring the results will be final and will be binding to all. No queries in this regard will be entertained.&lt;br&gt;


		<!-- &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prizes worth Rs 7000 to be won + intern from Internshala.com. &lt;/b&gt; -->
		</DESCRIPTION>	

		<RULES>&lt;br&gt;1.&#160; Please do not discuss strategy, suggestions or tips in the comments during a live contest. Posting questions clarifying the problem statement is ok. If you are unsure, email us at&#160;feedback@codechef.com&#160;  .&lt;br&gt;
2.&#160; Discussing CodeChef's problems or any aspect of problem, on any other platform on web, on identification, could lead to disabling of respective account and banning from the community.&lt;br&gt;
3.&#160; Almost all languages supported on CodeChef are allowed.&lt;br&gt;
4.&#160; Each program will be tested based on our critical test data. However output and input should be exactly as specified in the samples provided&lt;br&gt;
5.&#160; Please contact aditiagarwal@gmail.com or sinhashivam0406@gmail.com for any queries during the contest.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Judging Criteria:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
1.&#160; All the problems have same points alloted to them.&lt;br&gt;
2.&#160; Users are ranked according to the most problems solved.&lt;br&gt;
3.&#160; You can submit solutions as many times as you'd like, there are no penalties for incorrect submissions. Only your first correct submission will be considered.&lt;br&gt;
4.&#160; The total time is the sum of the time consumed for each problem solved.&lt;br&gt;
The decision of the organizers in declaring the results will be final. No queries in this regard will be entertained.&lt;br&gt;
5.&#160;Any participant found to be indulging in any form of malpractice will be immediately disqualified.
</RULES>

		<TIMELINE>
			&lt; Coming Soon /&gt; 
		</TIMELINE>
		
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/akraman.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Akraman Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		
		<CONTACTS>
			&lt;h4&gt;Shivam Sinha&lt;/h4&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;
				&lt;span class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-7770806859&lt;/br&gt;
				&lt;span class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;sinhashivam04@gmail.com
			&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/br&gt;

			&lt;h4&gt;Varsha Sachan&lt;/h4&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;
				&lt;span class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-8462876590
				&lt;/br&gt;
				&lt;span class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;
			&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/br&gt; 

			&lt;h4&gt;Aditi Agarwal&lt;/h4&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;
			&lt;span class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9407204899
			&lt;/br&gt;
			&lt;span class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;aditiagarwal@gmail.com
			&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/br&gt;
		</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES></UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>2</ID>
		<BACKGROUND>FuckingNoobs.jpg</BACKGROUND>	
		<TITLE>Techathlon</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>techathlon.jpg</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt;
			In the era of increasing efficiency, one has to multitask to reach his destined glory. For all the code maniacs out there who are ready for a coding extravaganza, Infotsav, this year is conducting Techathlon. From an Aptitude test in your own college, through an online coding round, to various onsite events at ABV-IIITM, Techathlon, at every stage, will put your knowledge, skills as well as logical ability to test. It is a 4-event technical extravaganza consisting of:-
			&lt;/br&gt; &lt;a href = "readmore.php?id=5"&gt;Algorithm Writing &lt;/a &gt;
			&lt;/br&gt; &lt;a href = "readmore.php?id=0"&gt;Bugspot &lt;/a &gt;
			&lt;/br&gt; &lt;a href = "readmore.php?id=1"&gt;CodeRush &lt;/a &gt;
			&lt;/br&gt; &lt;a href = "readmore.php?id=7"&gt;Code Stumble &lt;/a&gt;
		</DESCRIPTION>
		<RULES>
			&lt;/br&gt;1. &#160; TECHATHLON consists of 4 open-to-all events.
			&lt;/br&gt;2.&#160;  The participants should be the students of any IIIT.
			
			
			
			
			&lt;/br&gt;3.&#160;  Every member needs to participate in at least one of the above mentioned events.
			&lt;/br&gt;4. &#160;  No member can be in two TECHATHLON team.
			&lt;/br&gt;5. &#160;  Ties will be dealt with the scores of Code Rush.
			&lt;/br&gt;6. &#160;  The score of each event will be normalized. The contribution of each event     will be disclosed two weeks before the fest.
&lt;/br&gt;8. Disqualification from any event due to use of unfair means can lead to disqualification from whole TECHATHLON series.
		</RULES>

		<TIMELINE>

		&lt;/br&gt;1.&#160;  The first stage for qualifying to TECHATHLON would be an aptitude test conducted in their own Institutes.
		&lt;/br&gt;2. &#160; Second stage will be an online coding event.
		&lt;/br&gt;3.&#160;  The first 2 teams from each college to qualify the second stage will be eligible to participate in TECHATHLON.


		</TIMELINE>


		<!-- <DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/pinnacle.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Pinnacle Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS> -->
		<CONTACTS>
			&lt;h4&gt;AMANDEEP SACHAN&lt;/h4&gt;
		    &lt;p&gt;
			&lt;span class="phone"&gt;Phone:&lt;/span&gt;+91-9406987626
		        &lt;/br&gt;
		        &lt;span class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;amandeep.sachan@gmail.com
			&lt;/p&gt;
		    &lt;/br&gt;

			&lt;h4&gt;ANJALI MUNJAL&lt;/h4&gt;
		    &lt;p&gt;
		        &lt;span class="phone"&gt;Phone:&lt;/span&gt;+91-9009812385
		        &lt;/br&gt;
		        &lt;span class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;anjalimunjal001@gmail.com
			&lt;/p&gt;
		    &lt;/br&gt;
			
			&lt;h4&gt;VISHAKHA CHICHARA&lt;/h4&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;
				&lt;span class="phone"&gt;Phone:&lt;/span&gt;+91-8989415465
				&lt;/br&gt;
				&lt;span class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;vishakhachichra@gmail.com
		    &lt;/p&gt;
		    &lt;/br&gt;
			
		        
			

		</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>

	<EVENT>	
		<ID>3</ID>
		<BACKGROUND>U3W2SHOLWQ.jpg</BACKGROUND>	
		<TITLE>Hackathon</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>hackathon.jpg</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt;
			HACKATHON is one such event which promises to fill the veins of the audience with adrenaline and will make your knowledge cross all the borders. It’s an event in which the programmers and developers all around the globe to come together and collaboratively design and develop new apps or ideas and solutions to real life problems using latest technologies. Creative thinking inspires ideas and ideas in turn inspires change. This is sole motto of hackathon in which one needs to dive into particular data sets, problems or concepts and come out with a great innovative solution to one. The solution can be such as building a new data visualization, writing a document, presenting a code, developing an app or collaboratively investigating a problem.

 
		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;br&gt;
			&lt;ul&gt;
				&lt;li&gt;
1.&#160; All aspects of the Entrant Content must be originally created by and solely owned by you or in the public domain. All third party content and content unoriginal to you (unless it is in the public domain) is prohibited.  
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
2.&#160; Register for the competition simply on infotsav.com
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
3.&#160; The Entrant Content must be suitable for presentation in a public forum.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
4.&#160; Students and working professional from different institutes/organizations can come together to form team(s). 
 &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
5.&#160; Any identified act of plagiarism will be immediately disqualified.  
 &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
6.&#160; The teams should strictly adhere to the deadlines mentioned. 
 &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
7.&#160; The decision of the judges and organizers will be final and binding to all the participants. 
 &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
8.&#160; Any of the terms and conditions can be changed by the organizers anytime ensuring to give the participants appropriate time to respond to the changes. 
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
9.&#160; Participants will be judged on their Innovation and Creativity. 
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
10.&#160; Participants need to register to the event. Theme of the contest will be announced 10 days prior to fest. Participants need to work on the clip and present it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</RULES>

		<TIMELINE>

		&lt; Coming Soon /&gt; 

		</TIMELINE>

		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/pinnacle.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Pinnacle Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>
			&lt;h4&gt;Amar Prakash&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                &lt;span class="phone"&gt;Phone:&lt;/span&gt;+91-8989561895&lt;/br&gt;
                &lt;spanclass="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;amar.prakash196@gmail.com
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/br&gt;
			
			&lt;h4&gt;Akshit Agarwal &lt;/h4&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;
				&lt;span class="phone"&gt;Phone:&lt;/span&gt;+91-898913227
				&lt;/br&gt;
			    &lt;span class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;akshitagarwal@gmail.com
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/br&gt;

			&lt;h4&gt;Bhargavi Lingala&lt;/h4&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                &lt;span class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-7697403363
				&lt;/br&gt;
                &lt;span class="phone"&gt;E-mail:&lt;/span&gt;bhargavilingala2013@gmail.com
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/br&gt;
</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>

	<EVENT>	
		<ID>4</ID>	
		<BACKGROUND>U3W2SHOLWQ.jpg</BACKGROUND>
		<TITLE>S.C.R.U.D.</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>scrud.jpg</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt;The main purpose of coding has always been formulating a product to serve a purpose helpful for mankind.  Show your vision, apply your logics, type in your code and formulate a product pertaining to the given theme. Choose any platform from web, desktop software or android,  and make an efficient product. You will be judged on the basis of robustness, creativity, time and memory complexity. 
<!-- &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prizes worth Rs 12000 to be won  &lt;/b&gt; -->
</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>Coming Soon
</RULES>


<TIMELINE>

&lt; Coming Soon /&gt; 
r
</TIMELINE>


		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/pinnacle.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Pinnacle Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;ARPIT YADAV
&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone:&lt;/span&gt;+91-8718844237&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;yadavarpit@gmail.com
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;DEVASHEESH ROY
 &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone:&lt;/span&gt;+91-8090976918
&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;

                                                    &lt;h4&gt;EVI AGARWAL

&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-7587550000
&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail:&lt;/span&gt;evi.agarwal@gmail.com
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>5</ID>	
		<BACKGROUND>FuckingNoobs.jpg</BACKGROUND>
		<TITLE>Algo Writing</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>

		<IMAGE>algo.jpg</IMAGE>

		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt;An event to test the participants' problem solving and algorithm designing skills. Particpants will be given some problems and will be required to give a pseudo code containing step by step operations to be performed to solve that problem.
		You shall be judged on the basis of time  and space complexity of the algorithm you prosed.
<!-- &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prizes worth Rs 12000 to be won  &lt;/b&gt; -->
</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>Coming Soon
</RULES>


<TIMELINE>

&lt; Coming Soon /&gt; 

</TIMELINE>


		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/pinnacle.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Pinnacle Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;ANJALI MUNJAL

&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone:&lt;/span&gt;+91-9009812385&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;anjalimunjal001@gmail.com
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;VISHAKHA CHICHARA

 &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone:&lt;/span&gt;+91-8989415465
&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;vishakhachichra@gmail.com
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;

</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	
	
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>6</ID>	
		<BACKGROUND>FuckingNoobs.jpg</BACKGROUND>
		<TITLE>Jobs</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>

		<IMAGE>jobs.jpg</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt; A good campus placement is every graduate&apos;s deepest desire. But one needs to be fully prepared to face the toughest of the challenges that company poses to the candidates before recruiting their best fit. Therefore it becomes essential that the job seekers have sufficient knowledge and are well prepared for facing any test and interview. If they get job in their chosen and interested field, that will be a turning point in their life career. Only the best of the best get the chance of grabbing the jobs.
&quot;JOBS&quot; essentially focuses on preparing its participants for the campus placements at the same time ensures that the event as a whole is fun and exciting. It stimulates an environment of campus placements.

<!-- &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prizes worth Rs 9000 to be won.  &lt;/b&gt; --> 
<!--&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;-->
 
</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>Coming Soon
</RULES>

		<TIMELINE>

&lt; Coming Soon /&gt; 

</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/jobbureau.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Job Bureau Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Prakhar Dev Gupta&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9407512480&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;prakhar4edu@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
                                               &lt;h4&gt;Shruti Agarwal&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9407487312&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;shrutiag95@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;     
													</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>7</ID>
		<BACKGROUND>997348-code.jpg</BACKGROUND>	
		<TITLE>Code Stumble</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>codestumble.jpg</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt;Because writing code for a problem statement can be too mainstream, we have come
up with an amalgamation of coding and reverse engineering skills.
A two phase event which requires you to write a complete, working and complex code
for a given problem statement in the first phase and then frame the problem
statement for the code written by your competitors in the second phase.
Make your code tough for others to understand in first phase and understand the
gist of your competitor&apos;s code in second phase to maximize your chances of winning.
&quot;Your problem is your competitor&apos;s solution, your solution is your competitor&apos;s
problem.&quot;
</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
			1.&#160;  Event Structure:
&#160;  Rounds:&lt;br&gt;
Round 1: Coding&lt;br&gt;
Round 2: Decipher the code&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
2.&#160;  Languages Allowed – C/C++ , JAVA&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
3. &#160; Team Size – Maximum of 3 members&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
4.&#160;  The participants must reach the venue well before time.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
5. &#160; For Round 1, participants will be provided with a computer&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
6. &#160; A 15 minute break will be provided to participants between the 2 rounds.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
7.&#160;  Participants must adhere to the time limit.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
8.&#160;  Use of any unfair means will lead to disqualification of the team.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
9.&#160;  Use of internet is strictly prohibited.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
10.&#160;  No responsibility will be held by Infotsav, IIITM Gwalior for any late or lost
entries or other such situations.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
11.&#160;  Decision of the organizing committee will be final and binding.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;/ul&gt;
</RULES>

		<TIMELINE>
&lt;br&gt;
Round  1 : Coding&lt;br&gt;
Objective&lt;br&gt;
1.&#160; Write a program to solve a given problem statement.&lt;br&gt;
2.&#160; The program should run on all test cases provided beforehand.&lt;br&gt;
3.&#160; Time Limit&lt;br&gt;
45 minutes&lt;br&gt;
Round  2 : Decipher the Code&lt;br&gt;
Objective&lt;br&gt;
1.&#160; Decipher your competitor’s code and frame the problem statement for it.&lt;br&gt;
2.&#160; Print the output of given test cases.&lt;br&gt;
3.&#160; Time Limit&lt;br&gt;
30 minutes&lt;br&gt;
Judging Criteria&lt;br&gt;
1.&#160; A = Time taken to code in Round 1. (Max 45)&lt;br&gt;
2.&#160; B = Time taken to decipher the code in Round 2 (Max 30)&lt;br&gt;
3.&#160; F(x) = 4*A + 3*B (Max 270)&lt;br&gt;
4.&#160; Score = (1 / (1 + F(x)))*100&lt;br&gt;

</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/jobbureau.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Job Bureau Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;UTKARSH GOEL
&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9406507454&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;ugoel96@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
                                               &lt;h4&gt;LEKHANI AGARWAL
&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9009612389&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;SACHIN SHARMA

&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9530445348&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;sachinsharma.sharma2691998@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;                                                         
													</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>8</ID>	
		<BACKGROUND>quang-cao-hay-khong-quang-cao-de-ban-san-pham-tot-hon-large.jpg</BACKGROUND>
		<TITLE>Sameeksha</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>sameeksha.jpg</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt; The Annual Paper Presentation Conference is intended to encourage students to prepare and present meaningful papers and presentations on subjects relating to various domains (Technical &amp; Non-Technical).Researching, writing, and presenting a paper provides a student with invaluable early experience in expressing ideas related to its research area. 
<!-- &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prizes worth Rs 9000 to be won.  &lt;/b&gt;  -->
<!--&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;-->
 
</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>
			&lt;br&gt;
			The rules governing the competition are as follows:
&lt;br&gt;
	&lt;ul&gt;
		&lt;li&gt;
1. &#160; The competition is open to School students, undergraduates, postgraduates and research scholars.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
2.&#160;  Maximum number of participants in a Team is 4.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
3.&#160;  The topics that the papers need to be based on are suggestive. It is advisable that the presentation focuses on one particular topic. 
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
4.&#160;  Abstract should not exceed 150-300 words and the whole Paper should not exceed 20 pages.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
5. &#160;  The length of the paper should be between 1000 and 3000 words, not including the abstract, figures or tables.
	&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
6. &#160;  The oral presentation must not be more than ten minutes in length. Upon conclusion of each presentation, two additional minutes will be allowed for questions, for a total of twelve minutes.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
7.&#160;   Bring your college I-Card on the event day.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
8. &#160;  Please bring your PowerPoint presentation on a CD or in a pen-drive.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
9. &#160;  Soft-copies of the submitted paper and PowerPoint presentations must be in the .pdf format.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
10.&#160;   Please Mail your abstract, paper and PowerPoint presentation to sameeksha@infotsav.com.
   Difficulties will be addressed through the same email-id.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
11. &#160;  Please bring 2 hardcopies of the submitted paper on the day of the event.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
12. &#160;  Persons from different institutions can be a part of the same team. However, one person may not be a part of multiple teams for the same event.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</RULES>

		<TIMELINE>
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;



1. &#160;  The mail with submissions should contain:
    &lt;br&gt; a. Title- theme of the paper
     &lt;br&gt;b. Name of both the authors (with Institute’s name)
     &lt;br&gt;c. Contact no. of both the authors
     &lt;br&gt;d. E- Mail ID 
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
2. &#160;  Last day to submit soft copy of your report (via e-mail) will be seven days prior to the day of presentation.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
3. &#160;  After you have submitted the soft copy, a panel of judges will go through your material and if you are shortlisted to give the presentation, you will be notified.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
4.&#160;   The abstract mail should contain abstract, references, your e-mail id and mobile number. 
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
5. &#160;  The decision of judges will be final and no arguments or appeal will be entertained.
&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt;
</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/jobbureau.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Job Bureau Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;ABHISHEK SINGH
&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-8527520840&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;abhisheks043@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
                                               &lt;h4&gt;NISHTHA GAUTAM
&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9754630943&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;ANKUR SINGAL

&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-8458992188&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;singhalankur95@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;                                                         
													</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>

	<EVENT>	
		<ID>9</ID>	
		<BACKGROUND>ANI_1267.jpg</BACKGROUND>
		<TITLE>Brandsome</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>brandsome.jpg</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt;Brandsome is the advertising contest that is held under Infotsav. It is a noisy clamorous response to stimulus produced by crowd. It can also refer to reaction expressed over a period of time to an event. Advertising is a form of communication that typically attempts to persuade potential customers to purchase or to consume more of a particular brand of product or service. Advertisements are designed to generate increased consumption of those products and services through the creation and reinforcement of &quot;brand image&quot; and &quot;brand loyalty&quot;. Every major medium is used to deliver these messages, including television, radio, cinema, magazines, newspapers, video games, the Internet and billboards. This art of emphasizing desirable qualities so as to arouse a desire to buy has been molded in this event Brandsome.

		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;br&gt;Technical requirements:&lt;br&gt;
1.&#160;  Image submissions should meet the following requirements: &lt;br&gt;
Colored&lt;br&gt;
2.&#160;  Maximum size of 1920 X 1080 px&lt;br&gt;
3.&#160;  Horizontal or vertical orientation &lt;br&gt;
4.&#160;  In .jpeg , .jpg , .png format &lt;br&gt;
5.&#160;  With a limit of 5MB per image. &lt;br&gt;
1.&#160;  The video advertisement should not be more than 40 seconds long and should be in .mpg, .avi or .flv format.&lt;br&gt;
2.&#160;  In Video advertisement, flash presentation is also allowed.&lt;br&gt;
3.&#160;  The audio advertisement should not be more than 20 seconds long and should be in .mp3 or .mp4 format.&lt;br&gt;
Rules and Regulations:&lt;br&gt;
1.&#160;  The maximum size of a team is three.&lt;br&gt;
2.&#160;  The number of teams that would be shortlisted for second phase will depend on the number of teams in the first phase.&lt;br&gt;
3.&#160;  Teams participating without any unique id’s will not be judged.&lt;br&gt;
4.&#160;  The print advertisements should be targeting newspapers and magazines.&lt;br&gt;
5.&#160;  Once all submissions have been received, the judging and public voting phases for the competition will begin.&lt;br&gt;
6.&#160;  Entries not adhering to the rules and criteria may be excluded from the competition, at the discretion of the jury. The jury’s decision is final and there is no appeal.&lt;br&gt;
7.&#160;  In case of any discrepancy the organizers decisions will be final and no appeal from the participants will be entertained.
. 	Copyright and patents:&lt;br&gt;
8.&#160;  Submitted advertisement must be an original, unpublished work.&lt;br&gt;
9.&#160;  The entrant is responsible for the contents of the advertisement which cannot include copyright protected material. The entrant must have the rights for all the texts and images used in the submitted work. &lt;br&gt;


</RULES>

		<TIMELINE>
&lt;br&gt;
Phase 1:&lt;br&gt;
To participate in this Round the interested teams are requested to send their details on our mail.&lt;br&gt;
It is an online elimination phase. The participants have to send their print advertisement in the given domain and if you are able to send audio or video advertisement on our email-id. Keep in your mind that the print advertisement is indispensable.&lt;br&gt;
If you are fortunate enough to get through to first round you are eligible for phase2.&lt;br&gt;
You will be adjudged on the decision of judges (print and audio/video entry) after 48 hours of commencement of the round.&lt;br&gt;
Result will be published on our facebook page and the selected team will be intimated through mail.
 &lt;br&gt;
Phase 2:&lt;br&gt;
Top teams of round 1 will be called for round 2 which is on campus round and will held during INFOTSAV 2K16 .&lt;br&gt;
To participate in round 2 the teams should register physically at ABV-IIITM.&lt;br&gt;
In round 2 you will have to give the presentation on the given to topic.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
         Phase 3:
&lt;br&gt;
 In this round, we will give you a topic and you have to prepare your brand and presentation for the same, after this you have to present your brand and presentation, and you can play skit which will be describe your brand also.

&lt;br&gt;
</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/forex
		.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Forex Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Vaishnav Chandak&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9754054897&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;vaishnavchandak1996@gmail.com
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
													&lt;h4&gt;Utkarsh Yadav&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-8519043685&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;utkarshyadav.355@gmail.com
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
                                                    &lt;h4&gt;Shivani Mandeliya&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-7879216399&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;shivanimandeliya@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>10</ID>	
		<BACKGROUND>O717S80.jpg</BACKGROUND>
		<TITLE>Pinnacle</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>pinnacle.jpg</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt;If you have a unique idea that carves you out as a successful entrepreneur, then we welcome you to the most appreciated event of Infotsav. It provides your idea, a platform and eventually a spark just sufficient to ignite you. So what are you waiting for? It's show time. Pinnacle is the flagship event of Infotsav'16 which is being conducted on 8th and 9th October 2016. The event is attracting students from the best B-schools and Engineering colleges around the country. 
 &lt;br&gt;
 
Prize Money&lt;br&gt; 
First Prize: Rs.15000&lt;br&gt; 
Second Prize: Rs.10000 &lt;br&gt;
 
 
 </DESCRIPTION>	
		
		<RULES>&lt;br&gt;There is no registration fee. 
&lt;ul&gt; 
	&lt;li&gt;
1.&#160;  Executive Summary and all other documents/queries to be sent to pinnacle@infotsav.com
 &lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;
2.&#160;  A team should comprise of a maximum of 4 members. 
 &lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;
3.&#160;  Strictly adhere to the format mentioned below. 
 &lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;
4.&#160;  Students and working professional from different institutes/organizations can come together to form team(s). 
 &lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;
5.&#160;  Any identified act of plagiarism will be immediately disqualified. All conflicts subject to the jurisdiction of Gwalior Court only. 
 &lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;
6.&#160;  The teams should strictly adhere to the deadlines mentioned. 
 &lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;
7.&#160;  The decision of the judges and organizers will be final and binding to all the participants. 
 &lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;
8.&#160;  Any of the terms and conditions can be changed by the organizers anytime ensuring to give the participants appropriate time to respond to the changes.
&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;EVALUATION CRITERIA&lt;/strong&gt; 
 &lt;br&gt;
 	&lt;ul&gt;
 		&lt;li&gt;
1.&#160;  The clarity and potential of the market opportunity. 
 &lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;
2.&#160;  Innovativeness of business concept. 
 &lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;
3.&#160;  Feasibility of the plan. 
 &lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;
4.&#160;  The overall evaluation of potential reward to risk. 
 &lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;
5.&#160;  Marketing Strategy. 
 &lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;
6.&#160;  Financial Analysis. 
 &lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;
7.&#160;  Sustainability &amp; Scalability of Business Model. 
 &lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;
8.&#160;  Quality of presentation. 
 &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</RULES>

		<TIMELINE>

Phase 1: Executive Summary Submission (Online) 
 &lt;br&gt;
Last date for submission: 20th September 2016. 
&lt;br&gt;

Entries submitted after the deadlines will not be considered. 
 &lt;br&gt;
The Executive Summary will be submitted online in the PDF format only.
&lt;br&gt;
The PDF file can have a maximum of five pages excluding the cover page. 
. The pdf should be mailed to pinnacle@infotsav.com 
 &lt;br&gt;
Format for submission of Executive summary: 
 &lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;I. COVER SLIDE&lt;/strong&gt; 
 &lt;ul&gt;
 	&lt;li&gt;
A) Each entry should have a cover slide stating the Team Information of each member stated below: 
&lt;br&gt;Name 
&lt;br&gt;Contact No 
&lt;br&gt;Email-id 
 &lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;
B) The cover page must also contain the Project/B-Plan name, team name and the name of the institution. 
 &lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;
C) No reference of team members or their company/college is allowed anywhere in the executive summary except the cover slide. 
 &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;II. DETAILS&lt;/strong&gt; 
 &lt;br&gt;
The details of the executive summary should be in the following format: 
 &lt;br&gt;
 	&lt;ul&gt;
 		&lt;li&gt;

A. &#160;  The Purpose of the Plan&lt;br&gt; 
1. &#160;  The problem you are trying to solve through your plan&lt;br&gt; 
2.&#160;   Innovativeness of your idea (USP) &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;
B. &#160;  Market Analysis&lt;br&gt; 
1. &#160;  The characteristics of your target market (demographic, geographic, etc.)&lt;br&gt; 
2. &#160;  The products or services you will offer to satisfy those needs &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;
C. &#160;  The Company&lt;br&gt; 
1. &#160;  The needs your company will satisfy&lt;br&gt; 
2. &#160;  The products or services you will offer to satisfy those needs&lt;br&gt; 
 &lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;
D.&#160;   Marketing and Sales Activities&lt;br&gt; 
1.&#160;  Marketing strategy &lt;br&gt;
2. &#160;  Sales strategy &lt;br&gt;
3. &#160;  Keys to success in your competitive environment &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;
 
E. &#160;  Organization and Personnel &lt;br&gt;
1.&#160;   Key managers and owners &lt;br&gt;
2. &#160;  Key operations employees &lt;br&gt;
 &lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li&gt;
F. &#160;  Financial Data &lt;br&gt;
1. &#160;  Funds required and their use &lt;br&gt;
2. &#160;  Prospective financial summary (including a brief justification for prospective sales levels)  &lt;br&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
Results of selected Executive Summaries 
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
Will be declared latest by 25th September 2016
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

Phase 2: Presentation of final Business plans (On Campus) 
&lt;br&gt; 
The shortlisted teams will be invited on the campus for the presentation of their Final Business Plans. 
 &lt;br&gt;
15 minutes (13 minutes for presentation &amp; 2 minutes for binding) will be allotted to every team to showcase their complete B-Plan to the Judges. 
 &lt;br&gt;
Time constraints are to be strictly followed otherwise negative marking will be followed. 
 &lt;br&gt;
Teams are restricted to use Microsoft Power Point for presentations. 
 &lt;br&gt;
*The above mentioned dates are less likely to be changed or get delayed. 
 &lt;br&gt;
* For more details check www.infotsav.com   

</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS></DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Mayank Agarwal&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9959098212&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;mayankaa21@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
													&lt;h4&gt;Chahesh Chopra&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-7354732013&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;chahes96@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
                                                    &lt;h4&gt;Akhil Agarwal&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9407473508&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;akhilagarwal61@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
				<ID>11</ID>	
				<BACKGROUND>Smart-Cities-All-you-need-to-know.jpg</BACKGROUND>
		<TITLE>Smart Cities</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>smartcities.jpg</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt;&quot;The future of India lies in its villages&quot;- Mahatma Gandhi. Smart&apos;s Cities allows participants to develop solutions for villages to improve their condition. &lt;br&gt;
Participants are encouraged to submit their ideas for products or services that improve the lifestyle of the villagers and provide them a way to match the growth rate of towns and cities&lt;br&gt;
The participants are required to come up with there idea on developing the cities . The idea can be of field like medical,recycling, education,energy source etc..;&lt;br&gt;
		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>
	&lt;br&gt;
			Round1:It is an online submission round. You are required to prepare a ppt/abstract in 3 pages and mail it to the address given below before the stipulated deadline. The plan should clearly bring out the likely problems and solutions to the recommendations given by the teams. The PPT presentation should be mailed by oct 20 2016.
Our team will give a feedback on your presentation and participants should make the necessary changes according to the feedback and resend the PPT to our mail. The final PPT presentation must be mailed by 30 oct 2016.
&lt;br&gt;
Round2:Shortlisted teams from Round 1 would be invited to the ABV-IIITM, Gwalior campus for a proper presentation.
&lt;br&gt;
Notice:&lt;br&gt;
This competition is open to all students. Each team can comprise of a maximum of three members and should be from the same institute.The teams need to send their entries to tomorrow&apos;scities2K16@infotsav.com with the subject line and document name as Tomorrow&apos;sCities2K16_Teamname_Collegename.&lt;br&gt;
The body of the mail should contain the names of the team members,Course name, email Id and contact numbers.Register for the event by clicking on the link provided on the website for the same. The proposal should be in the pdf format.The decisions of the organizers and the panel of judges will be final and binding on all the participants.&lt;br&gt;
</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>

&lt; Coming Soon /&gt; 

</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/sameeksha.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Sameeksha Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Anshul Jain&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-7898135525&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;anshuljain614@gmail.com
	
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Bandra Ajay Kumar&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-7697674804&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;ajay.hn3@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
                                                    &lt;h4&gt;Nikita Chilivery&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-8435251866 &lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;nikitachilivery@gmail.com


                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
													
             
			</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>12</ID>	
		<BACKGROUND>FuckingNoobs.jpg</BACKGROUND>
		<TITLE>ITW</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>itw.jpg</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt;Waste management stands as one of the most debated political and environmental agendas. The ingredient demanded for the task to be accomplished is innovation, an idea to convert anything that can be regarded as waste into something that is creative and cool. The event aims at providing the knowledgeable youth an opportunity, to apply the existing technologies to transform 'waste to worthy'.
<!-- Prizes worth Rs 15000+ internship opportunity by CollegeFever to be won. &lt;/b&gt; -->
		<!--&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;-->
		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>Coming Soon
</RULES>

		<TIMELINE>

&lt; Coming Soon /&gt; 

</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/codeweavers.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Code Weavers Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Mahaveer Suthar&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9981326751&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;sutharm767@gmail.com 
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Amit Meena&lt;/h4&gt;
                                  &lt;p&gt;
								  &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-7665291798&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;unishubh1@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES></UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	
<EVENT>	
		<ID>13</ID>	
		<BACKGROUND>41..jpg</BACKGROUND>
		<TITLE>FOREX</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>forex.jpg</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt;This game provides a platform where the players can convert virtual money from
one currency to another. The player who has the maximum assets wins. The Foreign
Exchange market exists whenever one currency is traded for another. It gives a real time
experience of the "foreign exchange" provided with virtual money and real time data to get
the invaluable hand on experience.
<!-- &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prizes worth Rs 9000 to be won. &lt;/b&gt;
&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Visit: forex.infotsav.com &lt;/b&gt; -->
<!--&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : First Prize-Rs.4000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Second Prize-Rs.2000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;-->
		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>Coming Soon
</RULES>

		<TIMELINE>

&lt; Coming Soon /&gt; 

</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/webmania.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Web Mania Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
		&lt;ul class='download'&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/webmania.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Round 1 case&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>
													&lt;h4&gt;Shivam Sinha&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-7770806859&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;sinhashivam04@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
                                                    



		</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>14</ID>	
		<BACKGROUND>FuckingNoobs.jpg</BACKGROUND>
		<TITLE>Job Bureau</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>jobbureau.jpg</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt;Get to use the world's latest technologies and software. It's time for you to
experience the professional serene and achieve what you desire and are really capable of.
Infotsav gives you a chance to get placed before the actual campus drive in a virtual world
where you learn to be an efficient project leader and a skilled coder. The simulation takes
you into the flock of assignments where you move ahead by gaining experience and money.
The game checks your skills at choosing the right project at the right time, a single wrong
move could forestall your winning chances.
&lt;/br&gt;<!-- 
&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prizes worth Rs 9000 to be won. &lt;/b&gt; -->

</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>Coming Soon
</RULES>

		<TIMELINE>

&lt; Coming Soon /&gt; 

</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/La-Ingenious.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;La Ingenious Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
		&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/srsformat.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;SRS Format Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>
													&lt;h4&gt;Anshul Jain&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-7898135525&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;anshuljain614@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
                                                    
			</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES></UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>15</ID>	
		<BACKGROUND>FuckingNoobs.jpg</BACKGROUND>
		<TITLE>Trove Trace</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE>Online Treasure Hunt</TAGLINE>

		<IMAGE>trovetrace.png</IMAGE>

		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt;Does searching for a hidden treasure fascinate you? Are you enthralled by
clues and puzzles and want to step into the shoes of the master detective Holmes?? Then
look no further, Trove Trace is where you should be. There is nothing like a good riddle or a
clue to spice up your hunt. All the techno-freaks and pirates of the virtual world out there,trove trace is back - with murkier corners, crazier questions, more twists and turns to blow
your brains out, and a monstrous amount of fun.
<!-- &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prizes worth Rs 9000 to be won. &lt;/b&gt; -->
<!--&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;-->

 
</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>Coming Soon
</RULES>

		<TIMELINE>

&lt; Coming Soon /&gt; 

</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/trovetrace.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Trove Trace Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>
													&lt;h4&gt;Akansha Goel&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
                                                    
                                                    
</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>16</ID>	
		<BACKGROUND>FuckingNoobs.jpg</BACKGROUND>
		<TITLE>Snap Trap</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE>Online Treasure Hunt</TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>snaptrap.jpg</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt;&quot;Beauty lies in the eyes of beholder&quot; - Plato. Capture mesmerizing snaps from your camera and show the world your perspective of looking at things.  Click pictures and participate in the contest by uploading the pics on our official FB page. The snap with maximum mass appeal and engagement shall make way to the top seed.
<!-- &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prizes worth Rs 9000 to be won. &lt;/b&gt; -->
<!--&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;-->

 
</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>Coming Soon
</RULES>

		<TIMELINE>

&lt; Coming Soon /&gt; 

</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/trovetrace.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Trove Trace Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>
													&lt;h4&gt;Online Event&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
                                                    
</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>17</ID>	
		<BACKGROUND>CSGO-tournament-large.jpg</BACKGROUND>
		<TITLE>CS Go</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>

		<IMAGE>csgo.jpg</IMAGE>

		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt;Gamiacs is a blend of three most enthusiastically played games --Counter Strike 1.6, NFS MW and FIFA. 
Reload your guns and lace up your lucky boots because the biggest LAN gaming event of India is back. The stakes are high this time so head for the battle field, vanquish your enemy and show your might with the controller. With battle cries in the air and courage in your hearts, get ready for the kill. 

<!--&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;-->
		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>Coming Soon
</RULES>


		<TIMELINE>Coming Soon</TIMELINE>

		<DOWNLOADS></DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Archit Joshi&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9407203487&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;archit2693@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>18</ID>	
		<BACKGROUND>maxresdefault.jpg</BACKGROUND>
		<TITLE>COURSE CHASER</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>coursechaser.jpg</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt;
		The line follower will  be an event in which participants will have to compete with their line following robots in the given arena and beat their respective opponents in terms of accuracy and time limits. This  robot has to follow the black line on the white background, taking the right turns. The follower has to complete the race without losing the line.   
<!-- &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prizes worth Rs 11000 to be won. &lt;/b&gt; -->
		&lt;/br&gt;
		<!-- &lt;b&gt;Objective: &lt;/b&gt;
		Make a black line following robot. The time taken by the bot to traverse through the course will be one of the concrete criteria for determining the winner. The lesser the time taken the better the points gained by the bot.  If nobody finish the run, the farthest one run on tracks with maximum points will win.   -->
        </DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>Coming Soon
</RULES>

		<TIMELINE>

&lt; Coming Soon /&gt; 

</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;b&gt; Tracks &lt;/b&gt; To be uploaded soon..</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;SHUBHAM VARSHNEY
&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9458814904&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;shubham.07.var@gmail.com
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;ARPIT KHANDELWAL
&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9479917384&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;arpitkhandelwal2893@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;RITIK VERMA
&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9407510883&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;ritikxman@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;SHUBHAM GOEL
	&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-7693069100&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;itsshubham23@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;SURUCHI ARYA

	&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9893116203&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;suruchiarya30@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;                                                    
													
</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>19</ID>	
		<BACKGROUND>ANI_1142new.jpg</BACKGROUND>
		<TITLE>BLAZING WHEELS</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>

		<IMAGE>roborace.jpg</IMAGE>

		<DESCRIPTION><!--  &lt;b&gt;Introduction &lt;/b&gt; -->&lt;br&gt;
		Blazing Wheels is a  Robotics competition where Robots would be competing with each other in terms of speed and accurate control. There will be a race between two manually controlled robots. The robots should be controlled via remote control. Each team gets only one chance and the team completing first wins the race.
<!-- &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prizes worth Rs 11000 to be won. &lt;/b&gt; -->
		&lt;/br&gt;
		<!-- &lt;b&gt;TASK &lt;/b&gt;
		Design and construct a remote controlled  (wired/wireless) robot capable not only running fast but also is capable of fighting hurdles on the track in the least time.  -->
		
        </DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>Coming Soon
</RULES>

		<TIMELINE>

&lt; Coming Soon /&gt; 

</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;b&gt; Tracks &lt;/b&gt; To be uploaded soon..</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;SHUBHAM VARSHNEY
&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9458814904&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;shubham.07.var@gmail.com
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;ARPIT KHANDELWAL
&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9479917384&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;arpitkhandelwal2893@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;RITIK VERMA
&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9407510883&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;ritikxman@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;SHUBHAM GOEL
	&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-7693069100&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;itsshubham23@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;SURUCHI ARYA

	&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9893116203&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;suruchiarya30@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;                                                    
													
</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>	
	<EVENT>	
	<ID>20</ID>	
	<BACKGROUND>ANI_1455.jpg</BACKGROUND>
		<TITLE>ROBO SOCCER </TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>roboscocer.jpg</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt;
		Robo Soccer is a real time arcade game in which each bot is required to put a soccer ball in the desired area just like what happens in the game of football.   
<!-- &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prizes worth Rs 11000 to be won. &lt;/b&gt; -->
		&lt;/br&gt;
		
&lt;br&gt; To build manually controlled robot capable of playing soccer on an arena specially designed for robotic soccer match.  
		&lt;br&gt; The robot would compete against others in 1-1 matches. 
        </DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>Coming Soon
</RULES>

		<TIMELINE>

&lt; Coming Soon /&gt; 

</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;b&gt; Tracks &lt;/b&gt; To be uploaded soon..</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;SHUBHAM VARSHNEY
&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9458814904&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;shubham.07.var@gmail.com
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;ARPIT KHANDELWAL
&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9479917384&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;arpitkhandelwal2893@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;RITIK VERMA
&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9407510883&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;ritikxman@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;SHUBHAM GOEL
	&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-7693069100&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;itsshubham23@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;SURUCHI ARYA

	&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9893116203&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;suruchiarya30@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;                                                    
													
</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
	<ID>21</ID>	
	<BACKGROUND>ANI_1542.jpg</BACKGROUND>
		<TITLE>ROBO WAR</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>robowar.jpg</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt;
		Robo Wars is a real-time arcade game in which two opponents would be competing with their manually operated robots with the objective of immobilizing each other. The last robot standing would be the winner.Robo war will be held in two categories,namely :- 
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Robo War - &lt;/b&gt; The bots with weight between 20-40 kgs and size 60cm x 60cm x 80cm are eligible for this category.    
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mini Robo War - &lt;/b&gt;  The bots with weight less than 20 kgs and size 30cm x 30cm x 30cm are eligible for this category.   

<!-- &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prizes worth Rs 18000 to be won. &lt;/b&gt; -->  
		&lt;/br&gt;
		&lt;br&gt;
		Two bots will fight against each other in the arena. Their aim will be to overpower among opponents and throw them out of the arena, drop into the pit made in the arena. It will have fixed time duration.   
        </DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>Coming Soon
</RULES>

		<TIMELINE>

&lt; Coming Soon /&gt; 

</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;b&gt; Tracks &lt;/b&gt; To be uploaded soon..</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;SHUBHAM VARSHNEY
&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9458814904&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;shubham.07.var@gmail.com
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;ARPIT KHANDELWAL
&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9479917384&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;arpitkhandelwal2893@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;RITIK VERMA
&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9407510883&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;ritikxman@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;SHUBHAM GOEL
	&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-7693069100&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;itsshubham23@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;SURUCHI ARYA

	&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91-9893116203&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;suruchiarya30@gmail.com

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;                                                    
													
</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>22</ID>	
		<BACKGROUND>wpid-thumbnail-ee74f6fd8a150ce3cf50c7869376ef08-1050x688.jpg</BACKGROUND>
		<TITLE>Arthashastra</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>

		<IMAGE>artha.jpg</IMAGE>

		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt;The  quiz that challenges your brain, firing a volley of questions. Contest consisting of preliminary offline round and mains where the top scoring teamswill compete, to be the best.
		
<!--&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Prize Money
&lt;li&gt;First Prize : Rs.4000&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Second Prize: Rs.2000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;-->

</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>Coming Soon
</RULES>

		<TIMELINE>

&lt; Coming Soon /&gt; 

</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/analyst.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Analyst Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
		&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/Analyst_Case.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Analyst Case for Phase 1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;AKHILESH PUJARI
 &lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone:+91-8989529628 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail:unishubh1@gmail.com &lt;/span&gt;
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;

													
            </CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>23</ID>	
		<BACKGROUND>ANI_1341.jpg</BACKGROUND>
		<TITLE>Enigma</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE>The IT Quiz</TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>enigma.jpg</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt;
			A quiz is usually a form of a student assessment, but has fewer questions of lesser difficulty and requires less time for completion than a test.
		It is to celebrate this spirit that Infotsav conducts Enigma. Enigma will have a preliminary round of offline quiz and only the top scoring teams will compete in the mains, to be the best.
		So brace up yourself to be a part of techno- managerial quiz contest to compete with the best brains of the youth.
		This is the war of grey cells. So let us watch who meets the target superbly! We need your cooperation to move ahead in taking it to another level and achieve unfathomable level of excellence and popularity. 
		
<!--&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Prize Money
&lt;li&gt;First Prize : Rs.4000&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Second Prize: Rs.2000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;-->

</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>Coming Soon
</RULES>

		<TIMELINE>
&lt;br&gt;
The Enigma Quiz will consist of three rounds:-
&lt;br&gt;
	&lt;ul&gt;
		&lt;li&gt;
1. &#160;  Qualifying Round- Each team would be given a set of question paper containing multiple choice objective type. This round will be pen paper based round. 15 teams will qualify for the next round.
Time: 45 minutes
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
2.&#160;   Elimination Round –This will be PPT based round. Only 5 teams would be selected for Elimination Round.
Time: 30 minutes
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
3.&#160;   Final Round – Top 5 teams will meet in this final round which consists of several sub-rounds.
Time: 1 hr&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/analyst.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Analyst Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
		&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/Analyst_Case.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Analyst Case for Phase 1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Vaibhav Khandelwal &lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone:+91-8966989776&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail:vaibhavkhandelwal77@gmail.com&lt;/span&gt;
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Ashish Tiwari &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone:+91-9479915049&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail:191ashish@gmail.com&lt;/span&gt;
                                                 &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
													
            </CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
<EVENT>	
		<ID>24</ID>	
		<BACKGROUND>wpid-thumbnail-ee74f6fd8a150ce3cf50c7869376ef08-1050x688.jpg</BACKGROUND>
		<TITLE>Programmimg</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>programming.jpg</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt;A brain-storming session and test your coding skills; both the basics as well as the hidden lethal concepts of computer programming.
<!--&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;-->


</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>Coming Soon
</RULES>

		<TIMELINE>

The Programming Quiz will consist of three rounds:-&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
1.&#160;   Qualifying Round- Each team would be given a set of question paper containing multiple choice objective type questions based on syntax and logical understanding. This round will be pen paper based round . 15 teams will qualify for the next round.
Time: 45 minutes
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
2.&#160;   Elimination Round –This will be PPT based round. Only 5 teams would be selected for Elimination Round.
Time: 1 hr
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
3.&#160;   Final Round – Top 5 teams will meet in this final round which consists of three sub-rounds. These sub-rounds are listed below.
Time: 2 hr
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Sub-rounds:
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
1.&#160;   Buzzer Round: Each team will be provided with a buzzer. A set of questions will be asked and any team can answer it provided they hit the buzzer first. If the team answers correctly then they will be awarded points else adequate negative marking will be implied.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
2.&#160;   Jeopardy: Round will consist of a PowerPoint presentation format. There will be different set of questions, each having different points (based on their difficulty level). Each teams gets a chance to choose for which point question they would like to play. Each team will attempt one question at a time. The question once chosen by a team cannot be chosen back. Please note that the questions are initially hidden. The teams just need to choose on what point question they want to play. Once they choose then the question will be displayed. Negative marking will be there for almost all the question debarring few which are special questions. Special question can be of any kind for example some questions might not have negative marking or some question might have double points and so on.
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;
3. &#160;  Survival Round:  Each team must attempt the question given to them. If answered wrong then one member of the team should leave which they will decide among themselves. The team having the last member standing while all the other teams will have no member remaining after different cycles of questions will win the round.
&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;/ul&gt;

</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/enigma.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Enigma Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Vaibhav Khandelwal &lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone:+91-8966989776&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail:vaibhavkhandelwal77@gmail.com&lt;/span&gt;
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Ashish Tiwari &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone:+91-9479915049&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail:191ashish@gmail.com&lt;/span&gt;
                                                 &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
													
            </CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>25</ID>	
		<BACKGROUND>wpid-thumbnail-ee74f6fd8a150ce3cf50c7869376ef08-1050x688.jpg</BACKGROUND>
		<TITLE>Aptitude Quiz</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>aptitude.jpg</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt;An event to judge your critical thinking and analytical abilities.  Exercise your brain , think out of the box and crack the challenges. The topics involved shall cover verbal reasoning, non - verbal reasoning and basic mathematics.
<!--&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;-->


</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>Coming Soon
</RULES>

		<TIMELINE>

&lt; Coming Soon /&gt; 

</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/enigma.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Enigma Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;SHUBHAM SHARMA
 &lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone:+91-8225081628&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail:unishubh1@gmail.com&lt;/span&gt;
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;KRITI SINGHAL
 &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone:+91-9977192412 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail:hpal.261994@gmail.com &lt;/span&gt;
                                                 &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
													
            </CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>

<EVENT>	
		<ID>26</ID>	
		<BACKGROUND>FuckingNoobs.jpg</BACKGROUND>
		<TITLE>Anime Quiz</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>animemania.jpg</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>&lt;br&gt;'Otaku' is an trivia style anime quiz teams will compete each other ad answer questions from various anime shows featured on the weekly shonen jump and many more.


</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>

			&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
1.List of anime to be asked questions on:
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1.&#160;   Dragonball-Z&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2.&#160;   Naruto&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3. &#160;  Bleach&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4. &#160;  One Piece&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5. &#160;  Full Metal Alchemist&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6. &#160;  Tokyo Ghoul&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;7. &#160;  Attack on Titans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</RULES>

		<TIMELINE>

Anime quiz will proceed in Two steps
&lt;br&gt;
Round-1
&lt;br&gt;
Each team of at most 2 members will take on a quiz consisting of 30 MCQ style questions from above mentioned anime shows and the duration of quiz will be 30 mins.
&lt;br&gt;
Round-2
&lt;br&gt;
Top 6 teams who scored the highest in Round-1 will qualify to Round-2 which will be a on-stage 'Jeopardy' style quiz. The team having highest score will win. In case of tie a rapid fire round will take place to pick out the winner.
 &lt;br&gt;

</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/enigma.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Enigma Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;SIDDHANT SRIVASTAVA
 &lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone:+91-7748933480&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail:siddant.srivastava@gmail.com&lt;/span&gt;
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
													
            </CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>


	
	</EVENTLIST>
